What is that?!
Weren't Avdol's flames supposed
to be able to sense anything?!
Avdol, where are you?!
Avdol...
has been reduced to nothingness.
You were arrogant enough to
believe you could defeat Lord Dio.
Allow me to demonstrate
just how wrong you were.
You will fall in line, one by one,
as I scatter your atomic fragments
across the recesses of the Void.
It can't be!
I don't believe you!
Avdol's not dead!
Don't you lie to me!
What?
I never would have
imagined Polareth's stand
could attack this
swiftly from so far away.
An amazing feat to be sure.
Over here!
I want you to look at me when I kill you!
I'll see you
next
time.
It's coming to the end of the battle.
I'm going to hit the video of the world!
Stop it now!
It's the beginning of the story.
I'm going to take the moment.
I'm going to continue to go.
I'm going to continue to go. Crusaders.
The last page of the last page.
TATAKIKKOMEEND?
OF THE WORLD SONOCHI!
NO Kong.
All right, now I'm sure
something fishy's going on.
Ever since we escaped the Mirage,
I've heard the sounds of a battle.
Blast it!
Avdol and Polnareff are out there.
Damn that guy!
I know I hit the bastard, but
it wasn't enough to kill him.
He just swallowed himself again
so he could hide in that abyss.
Damn that guy in his stand!
Avdol, how could you do that?
How could you break the one
rule you gave us? Pull the ref!
Iggy, you have to get out of here now!
You told us we had to watch our own backs!
That you wouldn't save us
even if we were in danger!
You liar!
You've been meddling in
other people's business
ever since the moment
we set foot in India!
Dammit, Avdol!
Why couldn't you just leave me alone
and mind your own freaking business?!
If I hadn't ducked, I'd
be a dead man right now!
It's like fate is telling me to carry on!
This must be Avdol's way of
knocking some sense into me!
It's way too dangerous in here!
Let's get moving!
Come on, Iggy!
We have to make it upstairs!
Don't fall behind!
Look up ahead! It's the exit!
We're almost there!
But I won't just turn tail and run away!
Avdol sacrificed himself for us, and
I'll repay that debt no matter what!
He believed we had the power to
put an end to Dio once and for all!
I can't betray his faith
in us by letting him down!
That is not an option!
I refuse to take the easy way
out like some common coward!
I'm gonna see this fight
through to the bitter end!
The only place I'm running
to is Dio's shadow den!
So up the stairs we go!
I expected him to dash out the door.
Pity.
Impressive, he managed a hit.
It seems Polnareff's mental
fortitude gives him the
ability to conquer his fears
in the face of imminent death.
You will soon be joining
Avdol, rest assured.
Your strength pales in comparison to
the harbinger of death that is my stand.
If what he says is true, his stand's jaws
are the gateway to an alternate dimension.
A dark, unimaginable abyss.
One that allows him to move through our
realm without leaving any trace of himself.
But how does he do it?
And how the heck am I
supposed to beat him?
Oh, no, no!
He's cut us off!
He's nearby!
But where exactly?
Iggy, I need you to watch my back.
And don't worry, I'll do the same for you.
Okay,
if he wants to reach us, then he's going
to have to come out of that other realm.
This is good.
He has to come out from the
dark beyond at some point.
When he does, I'll take my chance and
attack him with everything I've got.
All right, come at me,
you demented pinball!
I'll slice you in two!
Now I pissed off so my
chariot's even faster!
I may have lost Avdol, but it'll be a cold
day in hell before I let you get away!
what the hell he he was
hiding under my foot
My foot!
Now you can't run away.
I got your foot so that
you can't hide anymore.
Eat silver!
I'll pass.
Mr.
Joestar, a brawl's underway!
Avdol and Polnareff!
Sounds like they came in after us and
wound up getting themselves into a fight!
Come on, you two!
We have to find them ASAP!
You've managed to hide
amid the chaos, Polnareff.
How futile.
You couldn't have gone
far with that injury.
Which means you're hiding
beneath the rubble.
By now you must have realized
you're helpless against me.
You shall meet your end by my hand.
Now then, where could you be, Polnareff?
That's quite the ruckus, Cool Ice.
Lord Dio!
Please be careful, my lord.
I believe Polnareff and that four-legged
rudin are still hiding nearby.
Allow me to handle the situation.
You mustn't trouble yourself
with such nonsense, Master.
A fake deal made from the fool.
We got him.
You'd think I'd feel guilty about
attacking from behind like a coward.
And you'd be wrong, because you
pulled the same shit on Avdol.
This is the death you deserve.
Now, Iggy, crucify him!
Make him pay for what he did.
End his life in the same
merciless way he did Avdol's.
Send him straight to hell!
You're kidding he knows
but how because the windows
to my left are letting in
the light from the sun?
Lord deal would never enter
this room during the day?
You'll suffer a thousand deaths!
for your deception.
Iggy!
I made a vow to Lord Dio that
I would kill you, interlopers.
He entrusted me with that honor.
Lord Dio's a man of his word.
He would never descend to the
second floor for any reason.
No, he's gonna kill Iggy.
He's about to be swallowed by the abyss.
Now die, you filthy, pathetic dog!
Your incorrigible ruse forced me
to destroy Lord Dio's likeness!
Did he really just hit him?
He didn't use the void!
Instead of killing Iggy,
he went in for a punch!
Do you know what you've done?
I don't care if it was a fake.
You forced me to destroy a
figure in the form of Lord Dio,
and you must answer for that crime.
Your life is mine now!
I will kick you to death!
My dark abyss could swallow
you whole in an instant,
but a quick death
wouldn't satiate my fury.
This whole mess, it's all your fault!
This is what happens
to those who anger me!
Have you learned your lesson yet?
How about it? Is this better?
Tell me! Is it? Is it? Is it?
Stop it! Leave him alone!
It's like Cool Ice's brain has melted!
Is he really going batshit
because he destroyed
some pile of sand that looked like Dio?
From over here, his
soul is the murky abyss.
It's a bottomless black
hole that obliterates
any and everything that gets in its way!
I was warned about the humans.
Lord Dio said the Resolve in their
hearts must never be underestimated.
But you, you're just a flea bitten stray.
You've never known Resolve, and you
certainly know nothing of pride.
You can't grin at this!
Leave him alone! You like that? Do you?
What did I say?
Come on, your suffering's just begun!
Cool Ice!
You're dealing with me now!
I'm ending this, Polnareff.
Damn it!
He's gone!
But more importantly, Iggy!
Our plan to trick Cool Ice
may have fallen through,
but your sand might have just saved us.
Thanks to you, I think I found
a way to find the bastard!
Yeah, that's him, all right.
I can see him moving around.
Guess your stand power
is a double-edged sword.
When you move, your stand has no choice
but to absorb everything in your path.
So choke on a mouthful of this and
get over here, you piece of shit!
As soon as you come out from behind
your stand's putrid teeth to attack me,
I'll turn the tables and finish you off!
Bullseye, yeah! Eat that!
Well, would you look at that.
I found your weakness, Cool Ice.
Any attempt to pinpoint my
location leaves you vulnerable,
which is probably a tad
inconvenient since you can't
see me without emerging
from your dark dimension.
It's over!
Now suck on my sword and
burn in hell, field de putt!
Hurry up and die!
What?
How are you still alive?
I skewed your throat and brain stem!
Would you die already?
No way you're getting out of it!
Hurry up and die! Die!
Stop making me repeat myself! Die!
I cannot die.
My mission is far too
important to feel any pain.
I will not rest until I kill you.
I'll swallow Iggy, the Joestars,
and anyone else who gets in my way.
Only after your deaths
will I allow myself to die.
Bastard!
There's a good boy.
You knew to withdraw your sword.
I also know that you're about to die!
This is the one.
The vile arm you used to stab me.
Knock it off!
Damn it!
I had no choice but to shove him away!
No!
You're not going anywhere!
Did I get him?
Where'd he go now?
Shit!
He got my leg!
I can't move!
But I can't think about
the pain right now.
I was so close, I almost
managed to land a killing blow.
But he got away!
This guy is different,
fueled by pure vengeance.
And he's not just nuts.
His devotion to Dio is all-consuming,
but I won't let him get the upper hand.
You said you couldn't die yet?
Well, I can't die until I kill you!
Okay, here he comes!
Take this!
Shit! It's no use!
His stand just obliterated
the tip of my sword!
Though it probably wouldn't
matter even if it were intact!
It's impossible to attack him
when he's hidden in the abyss!
If I so much as touch that
thing, it'll swallow me whole!
Great!
Now he's absorbing the
building at random! Mad!
That's clever.
He knows full well I'll go
after him if he shows himself.
So he's blindly attacking to
prevent me from fighting back.
He's not messing around.
At this rate, he's going
to hit me for sure.
I should pull back Chariot
and think of a plan.
Damn this isn't good.
He's not gonna last long if he keeps
losing blood from the state he's in.
I'd say his broken ribs
must have punctured his
lungs
and
just when I
thought this couldn't get
any worse.
Why the hell is he devouring the walls?
Wait a second.
I'm starting to think I was all
wrong.
This isn't random.
It was all part of his
plan from the beginning.
He's been drawing circles
around me.
And with every lap, he's
getting closer and closer.
The odds are stacked against me.
But I
have to do something.
He's closing in.
He still doesn't know our location.
But with that rolling ball
of death hurtling toward us.
It doesn't matter.
He's got us right where he wants us.
There's no way I'm gonna be able to dodge
an attack from him with this bum leg.
I've gotta try to escape
through the floor.
I don't have enough
time to tunnel through.
He's coming straight for us.
Somehow I dodged it.
Not out of the woods.
He's closing in on me like a
needle on an old record player!
I only have about five
more rounds before he makes
his way back here and
finishes me off for good!
So, the million-dollar question is,
how do I dodge with this injured leg?
If I had it my way, I'd just pick
option two, but I can't count on that.
They only entered the mansion
ten minutes before us.
As much as I'd love for
them to swoop in out of thin
air and save the day like
some American comic book hero,
wishful thinking's not gonna save me now.
There's no point hoping for
an out-of-the-blue rescue.
For all I know, the others might be
in the middle of a fight themselves.
All right, then.
Option one's our only choice.
Okay, Chariot, I need you to pull me
out of the circle as fast as you can!
What are you doing?
Pull me faster, Chariot!
It's no use!
What do you know?
The answer ended up being option three.
Life's a bitch!
Silver Chariot is a finesse-oriented
stand that fights with a saber.
It simply doesn't have the
power to pull my body weight,
especially when I'm injured.
I'm done for.
You're holding on by a thread.
Stay down, you stupid mutt!
If you keep moving or try
using your stance power,
your broken ribs will sink deeper
into your lungs and kill you!
Hey you can drop the
tough guy act you idiot
the only thing this will
accomplish is you dying
right along with me
just you wait
i'm the one
who's gonna save you you
have to live on to tell Mr.
Joestar and the others about this bastard
you have to defeat him in my stead?
Avdol might have saved me, but
you sure as hell better not!
If we all die here, then
what was the point of this?
One more loop, and it's lights out.
So it's number three.
Life can be a bitch sometimes.
We both wanted to win.
Guess he wanted it more.
Au River, Iggy. Woo!
Thank you.
the blood that stings my body is avdol's
handiwork I'm not privy
to all of the details.
You're right.
I had some pretty selfless friends, huh?
You're not going to defeat me!
This is how it always is.
I don't get it until after they're gone.